notjustalabel.com 2014-06-23

# Privacy Policy | NOT JUST A LABEL

Date of Last Revision: 14 February 2014

**INTRODUCTION**

NOTJUSTALABEL.com is dedicated to keeping your data secure and private. We will not share, resell, or distribute your personal information to any other company or entity, and any information you commit to us is for your own use and reference only, and for the benefit of the other members. We may track movements and communications on the site, and analyse statistics taken from data inputted into the site by users in order to improve our quality of service.

All images, video, writings, recordings, and all other digital media remain your intellectual property, however we reserve the right to distribute reproductions of work in a digital form only, however will never do so without your prior consent. 

If you have any questions regarding IP rights and privacy policies, feel free to contact us.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE BY NOTJUSTALABEL.com**

NOTJUSTALABEL.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the NOTJUSTALABEL.com service. NOTJUSTALABEL.com also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other.

NOTJUSTALABEL.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. 

User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the NOTJUSTALABEL.com social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join NOT JUST A LABEL, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network. Users within a personal network communicate on NOTJUSTALABEL.com with each other through the NOTJUSTALABEL.com service, without disclosing their email addresses. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, NOTJUSTALABEL.com allows users to search for other members using first and last name, and schools and/or companies where users may have attended or worked.

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. 

From time to time, NOTJUSTALABEL.com or a partner may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on NOTJUSTALABEL.com. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply. 

**INVITATIONS AND OTHER COMMUNICATIONS TO NON-MEMBERS**

NOT JUST A LABEL members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. NOTJUSTALABEL.com stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations. NOTJUSTALABEL.com does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations or invitation reminders. Recipients of invitations from NOTJUSTALABEL.com may contact NOTJUSTALABEL.com to request the removal of their information from our database. 

**USE OF COOKIES**

NOTJUSTALABEL.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from NOTJUSTALABEL.com in order to use most functions on the site. Please note that NOT JUST A LABEL allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the NOT JUST A LABEL Privacy Policy. 

**LINKS**

NOTJUSTALABEL.com contains links to sites. NOTJUSTALABEL.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on NOTJUSTALABEL.com. 

**JOURNALS AND WEBLOGS, MESSAGE BOARDS, CLASSIFIEDS AND PUBLIC FORUMS**

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to Journals, WebLogs, Message Boards, Classifieds or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

**CORRECTING/UPDATING OR REMOVING INFORMATION**

NOTJUSTALABEL.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as My Look Book and Account Settings.

**SECURITY**

NOTJUSTALABEL.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. NOTJUSTALABEL.com takes precautions to ensure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time For any additional information about the security measures we use on NOTJUSTALABEL.com, please contact us. 

**SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION BY NOTJUSTALABEL.com**

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, NOT JUST A LABEL will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: 

  1. to conform to legal requirements or to respond to an official request from the police or any duly authorised government agency or other legal process received by NOTJUSTALABEL.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; 
  2. to enforce the NOTJUSTALABEL.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or 
  3. to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. 

NOT JUST A LABEL reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of NOT JUST A LABEL or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below. 

**CHANGES IN OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days. 

**CONTACTING THE WEBSITE**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us.

© 2014 NOT JUST A LABEL All Rights Reserved.
